Hello friends, I am Ganesh Upadhyay,
Insurance Advisor. Friends, keep
meeting me on this YouTube. Yes, friends,
today we will talk about motor insurance.
Friends, in motor insurance,
today we will talk about extended warranty. Friends,
if we buy any vehicle, then
we get extended warranty in it. If we
buy a vehicle, then we
get warranty in it. Warranty means that if there is any
manufacturing defect, then
we get guarantee for it. Because
friends, the manufacturing defect
comes under our insurance claim
and neither does any garage owner do it.
So friends, it
comes under manufacturing defect, which is directly
fixed by the company. Many times
you must have heard that if there is any manufacturing defect in a vehicle or
any other item that you have bought, then the
company
calls back the entire item from the market because
it has a manufacturing defect.
Similarly, friends, many times manufacturing effect occurs in the vehicle also,
hence companies give warranty on it.
Some give 2 years warranty in these vehicles
and some give 3 years warranty,
so friends, there is a good news for you
that if you want to extend this
extended warranty, then there is
a
very good option for you that you
can extend the warranty of your vehicle for
2 years or 3 years, so
friends, if your vehicle has a 2 year warranty, then you can take an extended warranty of 3 years in it and if your vehicle has a 3 year
warranty, then you can take an extended warranty of 2 years, that is,
you will get it for a maximum of five years only and friends, the
sooner you take it on the vehicle, the
lower will be your premium, that is, if
you take it before 90 days, then the
premium will be some more in it, if you take it between 90 days to 180
days, then its
premium will be a little more and if you
take it after 180 days, then its premium will be more,
so the sooner you take this extended warranty
The sooner you take the warranty, the more
benefits you will reap. The lower the premium will be.
You
can avail this warranty before the warranty period ends, but if
your warranty period ends,
you will not get it after that. Suppose you have
bought a car and its
warranty is for 2 years, then you will have to take
this extended warranty before the 2 years are over.
If you
think of taking it after the 2 years are over, then you will
not get this warranty. And one more thing to keep in mind is that the
extended warranty,
whether you have got the insurance done
from any company, whether you have got it done from TA or from
any company,
then you
can get this extended warranty from ICICI Lord
because it will not have any effect on it
because the warranty you are getting is only
for the manufacturing defect. So friends,
this is a very good feature introduced
by ICICI Lord because there was a lot of demand from the people that the
manufacturing warranty of the car is for
very few years.  Considering the 2 years or 3 years, it has been found
that you
can take it for 2 years or 3 years further, so
if you need more information about it
or you want to buy it for your vehicle, then
you
can call me on the number written in the description and I hope
friends that you would have liked this video, so do
not forget to like and share it
and if you have not subscribed to this channel yet, then
subscribe to it too, so
friends, we will meet very soon with a new
video and new information, till then
thanks.